[MUSIC PLAYING]
Polycast与Rob Dodson提供#Ask Polymer
Hey there, Polycasters.
欢迎，Polycast所有者。罗伯。
I just wanted to welcome you to this brand
我很高兴欢迎您加入这个新的部分
new segment we're doing on our show called Ask Polymer.
我们已将其添加到名为Ask Polymer的程序中。
Every other week, we're going to do is.
每周我们都会
We're going to have you send in questions on a social network
通过在您选择的一个社交网站上收到您的问题。
You got some sort of crazy ear worm, something
如果你有麻烦的事
you want to know about Polymer, but you're not
或您想知道的关于聚合物的问题
quite sure about, you send those in, you hash tag it #askPolymer
还是我不确定的问题，请将其发送至#askPolymer标签
and we'll answer it.
我们会回答。
All right, question number one comes
好吧，肯尼斯的第一个问题
from Kenneth who writes in and asks,
谁发问，
didn't you mentioned that there would be a CDN for Polymer
您不是说可以使用聚合物的CDN吗？
or something like that?
还是类似的东西？请问这个工作很快吗？
Now in the past, we've actually encouraged people
过去，我们鼓励人们
not to use CDN with HTML imports because they
不要将CDN导入与HTML一起使用
would have a hard time de-duplicating
依赖项的重复副本将很难删除。
If they're all coming from different domains,
如果它们都来自不同的领域，
the de-duping mechanism can't really
该机制将删除重复项
figure out where there are copies of things.
您将无法识别复印位置。
But, at the recent Polymer summit,
但是在上届聚合物大会上
we showed off a new project we've
我们提供了一个新项目
been working on called PolyGit.
我们正在研究它，名为polyGit。
Addy Osmani did an entire talk, where he included PolyGit
Uday Osmani将现代术语称为polyGit
as one of the segments in there, showing how you could use it
作为该部分的一部分，展示如何在项目中使用它。
The idea with PolyGit is that it's actually
这个想法是PolyGit
kind of our own magic server.
请记住，这是我们的神奇服务器。
It uses the GitHub, the raw GitHub API, as kind of a CDN
它使用GitHub（初始GitHub API）
like thing.
作为一种CDN。
So it's great for experimenting, not quite ready for production
因此，在实验框架内效果很好，但尚未准备好发布。
though.
因此，您不能使用PolyGit
in a real project.
在一个真实的项目中。
But if you're doing something like a JS
但是如果您正在设计类似
Bin or a little sample you just want to show something off
JS Bin，或展示一些东西的小样本
on a prototype, it's perfect for that.
在原型上，您可以将其用于此。
And we hope, kind of in the long term,
希望从长远来看
that PolyGit will eventually be production ready.
PolyGit最终发布。
So that could be our CDN solution down the line.
因此，将来可以用作CDN解决方案。
So thank you, Kenneth, for sending that question in.
因此，谢谢肯尼斯（Kenneth）发送给我们。
Our next question comes from Andrew,
我们来自安德鲁的下一个问题，
who asks when will Polymer and Angular play nice together?
谁会问Polymer和Angular什么时候可以很好地协同工作？
So great question, Andrew.
很好的问题，安德鲁。
This is actually something a lot of people ask.
这是许多人问的问题。
They want to know about Polymer and Angular, or Polymer
他们想了解更多有关Polymer和Angular的信息，
and React or some other framework.
或Polymer，React或任何其他框架。
The main reason why many of those frameworks
框架难以运作的主要原因
have a hard time working with Polymer today
今天的聚合物是
is that pretty much all of them predate web components,
他们几乎全部都在Web组件之前，
and so they're not quite sure how to work
所以很难工作
with things like shadow DOM.
带有阴影DOM之类的东西。
Now, once we have Shadow DOM shipping natively everywhere,
现在，Shadow DOM在本地各处发布。
the story actually gets a little bit better, because it hides
情况会变得更好，因为那些框架会隐藏
and it sort of encapsulates a lot of the things
并封装很多东西
that the web components are doing behind the scenes
比Web组件在后台做的事
so the frameworks don't need to know about it.
因此，框架不需要知道。
But right now, we're still in the in-between place.
但是暂时我们还处于中间位置。
We've got polyfills for shadow DOM
我们为阴影DOM提供了自定义的polyfill
and that can trip up some of these frameworks.
这可能会揭示其他一些框架中的错误。
So when we get native Shadow DOM everywhere,
因此，当我们到处都有本地Shadow DOM时，
things will be a lot better.
情况会好得多。
Also, with something like, specifically
并有专门的东西
for Angular and Angular two, they've
对于Angular和Angular两个，特别是
been rewriting their data binding systems.
数据链接系统正在重新编辑。
It'll work better with the sort of events
在某些情况下会更好地工作
that Polymer elements fire, and they'll also
发射聚合物元素，您将能够
be able to handle Shadow DOM better.
通过更好地处理Shadow DOM。
They've got a whole sort of Shadow Dom renderer
他们有一台Shadow DOM投影仪，这就是他们的工作。
So thank you, Andrew, really great question.
谢谢安德鲁的伟大问题。
All right, our next question comes
好的下一个问题
from Rory, who asks what is your favorite custom element?
罗里在问谁，您最喜欢的物品是什么？
This is a pretty good question.
这是一个很好的问题。
Thank you, Rory, for sending that in.
感谢Rory发送。
My favorite custom element is either iron-localstorage or
我喜欢的自定义商品是铁本地存储或
iron-ajax, which we just did an episode on.
iron-ajax，我们记录了一个情节。
So you can actually go back and watch
你可以回去看
the previous episode of Polycast,
Polycast的上一集，
learn all about how to use that element.
并了解所有有关如何使用此元素的信息。
And the reason why I like both of these
我喜欢这两个元素的原因是
is because they're nice declarative data providers.
因为它们充当元数据提供者。
So I can just sort of wire them up in my application.
所以我可以在我的应用程序中将它们链接在一起。
And then persist some data or fetch some data,
然后继续一些数据或查找一些数据，
and I don't have to write like any JavaScript
我不必像任何JavaScript一样写
to do that, which, I don't know, it just
要做到这一点
makes it a lot easier for me to build apps.
它只是促进应用程序设计。
So thank you, Rory, really great question.
谢谢罗里这个大问题。
Our next question comes from Andre,
我们来自安德烈的下一个问题
who asks why did Polymer choose to use
谁问为什么聚合物选择使用
Bower as its package manager and what about something like MPM?
Bower成为他的包裹经理，为什么不选择MPM之类的东西呢？
Are there plans to switch to that in the future?
有未来过渡的计划吗？
So, great question, Andre.
很好的问题，安德烈。
The reason why we originally went with Bower
我们最初选择Bower的原因
is because it gives you this nice, flat dependency structure
是因为它为您提供了良好而稳定的依赖关系结构
when it installs everything.
在安装所有内容时。
And that's really important for HTML imports.
这对于HTML导入非常重要。
MPM, on the other hand, tends to nest things
另一方面，MPM更喜欢存储东西
and that can kind of confuse the system.
这可能导致系统混乱。
Now, in MPM three, they've done a lot of work
目前在MPM3，他们做了很多工作
to improve on this de-duplication mechanism.
改进此重复删除机制。
So now you can get flat directories in MPM three
现在您可以在MPM3中获取静态目录
but the one thing that you can't do is conflict resolution.
但是，您无法解决冲突。
And that's actually really important for us.
这很重要。
We want to make sure that people aren't installing or getting
我们要确保没有人安装
the wrong version of something and getting some weird errors.
或得到错误的副本和一些奇怪的错误。
So in a future version of MPM, it
因此，在MPM的未来版本中，
sounds like they're going to fix that and, at that point,
看来他们会解决此问题，然后
we'll probably switch over to using that
我们可能会使用它
as our package manager.
作为我们的包裹经理。
So thank you, Andre, really great question.
谢谢安德烈的大问题。
All right, our last question comes
好，我们最后一个问题
from David, who asks, Mozilla has recently
来自问大卫的人，Mozilla最近说
said that they're not going to implement HTML imports,
他们不会执行HTML导入，
instead preferring ES6 modules.
他们更喜欢实现ES6模块。
So what are your thoughts about that?
您如何看待？
So great question, David.
很好的问题，大卫。
We actually talked about this a little bit
我们谈了一点
at the Polymer summit, so check that out over here.
在Polymer Conference上，您可以在这里观看。
And basically the long and short of it
摘要是
is Mozilla has said that they're not implementing them yet.
Mozilla表示他们尚未这样做。
They didn't say that they're never going to implement them.
但是他们没有表示他们将永远不会执行它。最近我们工作很忙
on the loader spec recently, which is what, under the hood,
装载机规格是
both modules and imports depend upon.
模块和可靠的进口。
And what we'd like to maybe see in the future
以及我们将来希望看到的
is perhaps both systems using the same mechanism
在实施的掩盖下，两个系统使用相同的机制。
And then you could have modules as the imperative flavor,
然后，您可能具有强制性的模块，
you could have imports as the declarative flavor,
而且您有导入定义，
and developers could benefit from both.
开发人员可以同时利用两者。
So that is the long term plan.
这是长期计划。
We're going to continue working with Mozilla on that,
我们将继续在此方面与Mozilla合作，我们将看到将要实现的目标。
So again thank you, David.
再次感谢大卫。
Really great question.
很好的问题。
Thank you all who sent in those questions.
感谢所有向我们发送问题的人。
A lot of really great stuff we didn't get to everything
我们还没有讨论很多美好的事情
but we're going to try to get to them in our future episodes.
但是我们将在以后的几集中尝试讨论它们。
So be sure to click that little subscribe button
因此，请务必点击此处的共享按钮
down there so you can get notifications
在下面接收我们的通知
as those roll out.
随着新的情节。
If you yourself have questions, you
如果您有任何疑问，
can leave them down in the comments 0
您可以在下面的评论中留下它
or ping us on a social network of your choosing
或在您选择的任何社交媒体上将其留给我们
at hash tag #askPolymer.
在#askPolymer主题标签上。
As always, thank you so much for watching
谢谢收看
and I'll see you next time.
下次见。
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[音乐]